<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"><channel><title><![CDATA[Sweet and Sour]]></title><description><![CDATA[A show about this Asian American life]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm</link><image><url>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png</url><title>Sweet and Sour</title><link>http://sweetandsour.fm</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 22:46:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/episodes.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[2016 Sweet and Sour FM]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><managingEditor><![CDATA[to.kzhu@gmail.com (katie zhu)]]></managingEditor><webMaster><![CDATA[to.kzhu@gmail.com (katie zhu)]]></webMaster><docs>https://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs><ttl>60</ttl><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asian America]]></category><itunes:subtitle>A show about this Asian American life</itunes:subtitle><itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:summary>Sweet and Sour is a show exploring different facets of Asian American life.</itunes:summary><itunes:owner><itunes:name>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:name><itunes:email>to.kzhu@gmail.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png"/><itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture"><itunes:category text="Personal Journals"/></itunes:category><item><title><![CDATA[Preview: Welcome to Sweet and Sour]]></title><description><![CDATA[A preview of Sweet and Sour, a podcast exploring different facets of the Asian American experience.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b0tm4642pe0g02pb3e70.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-teaser.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b0tm4642pe0g02pb3e70.m4a" length="5098700" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>A preview of Sweet and Sour, a podcast exploring different facets of the Asian American experience.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png"/><itunes:duration>5:43</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[1: The Contradictions of Being Asian American]]></title><description><![CDATA[For our first episode, katie and Nicole discuss their Chinese to American ratio with their parents, Jiming and Li, who also shared their perspective on raising kids in America. katie and Nicole discuss the contradictions of being Asian American, both as a model minority and persistent other. The Book and Essay Club kicks off with Erika Lee's "The Making of Asian America." On Hella Asian, Nicole investigates the ubiquity of the Danish cookie tins.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b1de7qetij4002gjh9t0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode1.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b1de7qetij4002gjh9t0.m4a" length="21646802" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>katie and Nicole talk to their parents, Jiming and Li, about their Chinese to American ratio. The Book and Essay Club kicks off with Erika Lee&apos;s &quot;The Making of Asian America.&quot; On Hella Asian, Nicole investigates the ubiquity of the Danish cookie tins.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode1.png"/><itunes:duration>24:19</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[2: Swintoning]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week, katie and Nicole dive into diversity in Hollywood, centered on a discussion of Margaret Cho and Tilda Swinton’s quest for racial absolution. On the new Can We Not segment: Rappers who only shout out Asian women with references to Chinese takeout... can we not? And you'll hear some tips and tricks about food storage on Hella Asian.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b1pvk03hi06g02obhfe0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode2.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b1pvk03hi06g02obhfe0.m4a" length="18841874" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>We discuss diversity in Hollywood and analyze the Tilda Swinton emails to Margaret Cho. Can we not only shoutout Asian women in rap with references to Chinese takeout? On Hella Asian, learn some tips and tricks for leveling up your food storage game.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode2.png"/><itunes:duration>21:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[3: Exploring Culture Through Art]]></title><description><![CDATA[On this week's episode, Felicia Liang joins us for a conversation on art, culture, and everything in between. We talk about her #100daysians project, her creative process, and what's next. On Hella Asian, Felicia flexes her abacus skills and we bond over the shared burden of weekend Chinese school. Can We Not Steve Harvey? katie and Nicole dive into the TV personality's offensive remarks about Asian American men.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b25tlfggu49002qro3j0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode3.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b25tlfggu49002qro3j0.m4a" length="28411773" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Felicia Liang of #100daysians joins us for a conversation on art, culture, and more. On Hella Asian, Felicia flexes her abacus skills. Can We Not, Steve Harvey? katie and Nicole dive into his offensive remarks about Asian American men.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode3.png"/><itunes:duration>21:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[4: The Racialization of Popchips]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week, we hang out with Priya Krishnakumar, a visual journalist at the LA Times. We talk to Priya about her overachieving parents, her insecurities as an Indian American, and she gives us her take on the state South Asians in Hollywood. We also swoon over Dev Patel and roast Ashton Kutcher for racializing Popchips. On Hella Asian, Priya recounts the power of a ganesha doll in exterminating pests. On IRL, Nicole recaps a panel on the Asian American community's needs in the time of Trump. ScarJo... Can We Not?]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b2lludm713n002v9lgg0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode4.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b2lludm713n002v9lgg0.m4a" length="25892271" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Priya Krishnakumar, a visual journalist at the LA Times, talks about her Indian American identity, South Asian representation in pop culture, and more. On IRL, Nicole recaps a political panel and ScarJo: Can We Not perpetuate white feminism?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode4.png"/><itunes:duration>28:01</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[5: You Need Less Face]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elise Hu joins us this week as Sweet and Sour's first foreign correspondent. Elise works for NPR and is based in Seoul. We talk to her about gender stereotypes in Korea and Japan, discuss Asian fetish and its ~consequences~, and what it's like to raise biracial kids in the time of Trump. On Hella Asian, Elise shares her love of Asian convenience stores.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b2upbts6jqv0010p15d0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode5.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b2upbts6jqv0010p15d0.m4a" length="34195139" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Elise Hu joins us as Sweet and Sour&apos;s first foreign correspondent. Elise works for NPR in Seoul. We talk to her about gender stereotypes in Korea and Japan, discuss Asian fetish and its ~consequences~, and her experience raising biracial children.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode5.png"/><itunes:duration>36:45</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[6: Of Bananas and Coconuts]]></title><description><![CDATA[Preetisha Sen joins us on the pod this week, a proud coconut—brown on the outside, white on the inside. Preetisha talks to us about growing up Indian American, why being Asian American doesn't mean she's always in a constant identity crisis, and how she thinks about religion through her experiences with Hinduism and Christianity. She also shares a Hella Indian story about her family on this week's Hella Asian. Plus: Can We Not... always assume the Asian woman is the nanny? kthx.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b38d1aqtm1a0010nvk40.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode6.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b38d1aqtm1a0010nvk40.m4a" length="25234851" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Preetisha Sen, a proud coconut (brown on the outside white on the inside), discusses religion &amp; tells us why being Asian American doesn&apos;t mean constant identity crisis. She shares a Hella Indian story, plus: Can We Not assume an Asian woman is the nanny?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode6.png"/><itunes:duration>27:42</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[7: The Origins of the Model Minority Myth]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ellen Wu joins us this week to discuss her book, "The Color of Success: Asian Americans and the Origins of the Model Minority."  Ellen breaks down Asian American history from the 1920s onward, analyzing the contradiction of the model minority myth being rooted in both inclusion and exclusion. We dive into race-making, geopolitical dimensions of Asian American identity, and the effect of the model minority on other groups such as Blacks, Latinx, South Asian and Southeast Asians. Ellen also unpacks the role that Asian American communities played in the formation of their own stereotypes.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b3qgqnd75hag010dsg20.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode7.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b3qgqnd75hag010dsg20.m4a" length="35022886" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Ellen Wu joins us to discuss her book, &quot;The Color of Success: Asian Americans &amp; the Origins of the Model Minority.&quot; We unpack the effect of the model minority on other groups and the role of Asian Americans in the formation of their own stereotypes.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode7.png"/><itunes:duration>40:38</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[8: Eat Bitter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jason Shen joins us this week to discuss the Asian American Man Study, an annual survey of the experiences and perspectives of American men of East, Southeast, and South Asian descent. Jason breaks down the 2016 results, discussing demographics, race and identity, stereotypes, media, dating, politics, and religion. We also chat about his views on masculinity as an Asian American man. On Hella Asian, Jason brings up an hot button issue: shoe-free households.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b48c8gqba5t0015isbhg.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode8.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b48c8gqba5t0015isbhg.m4a" length="32006162" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Jason Shen discusses the results of the 2016 Asian American Man Study, an annual survey of East, Southeast, and South Asian American men. We chat identity, stereotypes, and masculinity. On Hella Asian, Jason espouses shoe-free households.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode8.png"/><itunes:duration>36:38</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[9: Creating Spaces for Women of Color in Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[We chat with Kaitlin Gu, a software engineer at Google and the cofounder of Flawless Hacks, an annual Beyoncé-themed hackathon for women by women. Kaitlin shares her experience as an Asian woman in technology and tells us about how Flawless Hacks started. We discuss her passion for education and how she’s shaped Flawless Hacks to be a collaborative, non-competitive space for women in technology. On Hella Asian, we swap dating expectations our Asian parents have for us.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b4mqhrhg592g01599lv0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode9.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b4mqhrhg592g01599lv0.m4a" length="29120564" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>We chat with Kaitlin Gu, a software engineer at Google and cofounder of Flawless Hacks. She shares her experience as an Asian woman in technology and her passion for education. On Hella Asian, we swap parents’ dating expectations.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode9.png"/><itunes:duration>32:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[10: Power and Poké: Authenticity and Gentrification of Asian Food]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sonia Chopra, the managing editor of Eater.com, joins us this week to discuss Asian food trends and how certain foods reach the mainstream, who gets to be an authority on ethnic cuisine, and the importance of authenticity in popularizing food that isn’t yours. Why hasn’t Indian food enjoyed the same success and popularity like ramen or matcha? She also dives into Eater’s approach to covering food and its intersections with other aspects of society in diverse and holistic ways. We chat briefly about self-care and the p-word, and Sonia tells us what she does that’s Hella Asian.]]></description><link>http://bumpers.fm/e/b4sqp2t5t5q0017adgk0.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audiosweet-and-sour-episode9.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://bumpers.fm/e/b4sqp2t5t5q0017adgk0.m4a" length="29120564" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Sonia Chopra, the managing editor of Eater, talks Asian food trends and the importance of authenticity in popularizing food that isn’t yours. She also discusses Eater’s approach to covering food and its intersections in diverse and holistic ways.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode10.png"/><itunes:duration>32:29</itunes:duration></item></channel></rss>