<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"><channel><title><![CDATA[Sweet and Sour]]></title><description><![CDATA[A show about this Asian American life]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm</link><image><url>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png</url><title>Sweet and Sour</title><link>http://sweetandsour.fm</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 21:36:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/episodes.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[2016 Sweet and Sour FM]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><managingEditor><![CDATA[to.kzhu@gmail.com (katie zhu)]]></managingEditor><webMaster><![CDATA[to.kzhu@gmail.com (katie zhu)]]></webMaster><docs>https://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs><ttl>60</ttl><category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category><category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category><category><![CDATA[Asian America]]></category><itunes:subtitle>A show about this Asian American life</itunes:subtitle><itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:summary>Sweet and Sour is a show exploring different facets of Asian American life.</itunes:summary><itunes:owner><itunes:name>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:name><itunes:email>to.kzhu@gmail.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png"/><itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture"><itunes:category text="Personal Journals"/></itunes:category><item><title><![CDATA[Preview: Welcome to Sweet and Sour]]></title><description><![CDATA[A preview of Sweet and Sour, a podcast exploring different facets of the Asian American experience.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-teaser.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-teaser.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-teaser.m4a" length="5098700" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>A preview of Sweet and Sour, a podcast exploring different facets of the Asian American experience.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/sweetandsour.png"/><itunes:duration>5:43</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[1: The Contradictions of Being Asian American (ft. Jiming Zhu and Li Huo)]]></title><description><![CDATA[For our first episode, katie and Nicole discuss their Chinese to American ratio with their parents, Jiming and Li, who also shared their perspective on raising kids in America. katie and Nicole discuss the contradictions of being Asian American, both as a model minority and persistent other. The Book and Essay Club kicks off with Erika Lee's "The Making of Asian America." On Hella Asian, Nicole investigates the ubiquity of the Danish cookie tins.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode1.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode1.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode1.m4a" length="21646802" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>katie and Nicole talk to their parents, Jiming and Li, about their Chinese to American ratio. The Book and Essay Club kicks off with Erika Lee&apos;s &quot;The Making of Asian America.&quot; On Hella Asian, Nicole investigates the ubiquity of the Danish cookie tins.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode1.png"/><itunes:duration>24:19</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[2: Swintoning]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week, katie and Nicole dive into diversity in Hollywood, centered on a discussion of Margaret Cho and Tilda Swinton’s quest for racial absolution. On the new Can We Not segment: Rappers who only shout out Asian women with references to Chinese takeout... can we not? And you'll hear some tips and tricks about food storage on Hella Asian.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode2.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode2.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode2.m4a" length="18841874" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>We discuss diversity in Hollywood and analyze the Tilda Swinton emails to Margaret Cho. Can we not only shoutout Asian women in rap with references to Chinese takeout? On Hella Asian, learn some tips and tricks for leveling up your food storage game.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode2.png"/><itunes:duration>21:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[3: Exploring Culture Through Art (ft. Felicia Liang)]]></title><description><![CDATA[On this week's episode, Felicia Liang joins us for a conversation on art, culture, and everything in between. We talk about her #100daysians project, her creative process, and what's next. On Hella Asian, Felicia flexes her abacus skills and we bond over the shared burden of weekend Chinese school. Can We Not Steve Harvey? katie and Nicole dive into the TV personality's offensive remarks about Asian American men.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode3.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode3.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode3.m4a" length="28411773" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Felicia Liang of #100daysians joins us for a conversation on art, culture, and more. On Hella Asian, Felicia flexes her abacus skills. Can We Not, Steve Harvey? katie and Nicole dive into his offensive remarks about Asian American men.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode3.png"/><itunes:duration>21:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[4: The Racialization of Popchips (ft. Priya Krishnakumar)]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week, we hang out with Priya Krishnakumar, a visual journalist at the LA Times. We talk to Priya about her overachieving parents, her insecurities as an Indian American, and she gives us her take on the state South Asians in Hollywood. We also swoon over Dev Patel and roast Ashton Kutcher for racializing Popchips. On Hella Asian, Priya recounts the power of a ganesha doll in exterminating pests. On IRL, Nicole recaps a panel on the Asian American community's needs in the time of Trump. ScarJo... Can We Not?]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode4.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode4.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode4.m4a" length="25892271" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Priya Krishnakumar, a visual journalist at the LA Times, talks about her Indian American identity, South Asian representation in pop culture, and more. On IRL, Nicole recaps a political panel and ScarJo: Can We Not perpetuate white feminism?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode4.png"/><itunes:duration>28:01</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[5: You Need Less Face (ft. Elise Hu)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elise Hu joins us this week as Sweet and Sour's first foreign correspondent. Elise works for NPR and is based in Seoul. We talk to her about gender stereotypes in Korea and Japan, discuss Asian fetish and its ~consequences~, and what it's like to raise biracial kids in the time of Trump. On Hella Asian, Elise shares her love of Asian convenience stores.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode5.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode5.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode5.m4a" length="34195139" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Elise Hu joins us as Sweet and Sour&apos;s first foreign correspondent. Elise works for NPR in Seoul. We talk to her about gender stereotypes in Korea and Japan, discuss Asian fetish and its ~consequences~, and her experience raising biracial children.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode5.png"/><itunes:duration>36:45</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[6: Of Bananas and Coconuts (ft. Preetisha Sen)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Preetisha Sen joins us on the pod this week, a proud coconut—brown on the outside, white on the inside. Preetisha talks to us about growing up Indian American, why being Asian American doesn't mean she's always in a constant identity crisis, and how she thinks about religion through her experiences with Hinduism and Christianity. She also shares a Hella Indian story about her family on this week's Hella Asian. Plus: Can We Not... always assume the Asian woman is the nanny? kthx.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode6.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode6.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode6.m4a" length="25234851" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Preetisha Sen, a proud coconut (brown on the outside white on the inside), discusses religion &amp; tells us why being Asian American doesn&apos;t mean constant identity crisis. She shares a Hella Indian story, plus: Can We Not assume an Asian woman is the nanny?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode6.png"/><itunes:duration>27:42</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[7: The Origins of the Model Minority Myth (ft. Ellen Wu)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ellen Wu joins us this week to discuss her book, "The Color of Success: Asian Americans and the Origins of the Model Minority."  Ellen breaks down Asian American history from the 1920s onward, analyzing the contradiction of the model minority myth being rooted in both inclusion and exclusion. We dive into race-making, geopolitical dimensions of Asian American identity, and the effect of the model minority on other groups such as Blacks, Latinx, South Asian and Southeast Asians. Ellen also unpacks the role that Asian American communities played in the formation of their own stereotypes.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode7.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode7.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode7.m4a" length="35022886" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Ellen Wu joins us to discuss her book, &quot;The Color of Success: Asian Americans &amp; the Origins of the Model Minority.&quot; We unpack the effect of the model minority on other groups and the role of Asian Americans in the formation of their own stereotypes.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode7.png"/><itunes:duration>40:38</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[8: Eat Bitter (ft. Jason Shen)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jason Shen joins us this week to discuss the Asian American Man Study, an annual survey of the experiences and perspectives of American men of East, Southeast, and South Asian descent. Jason breaks down the 2016 results, discussing demographics, race and identity, stereotypes, media, dating, politics, and religion. We also chat about his views on masculinity as an Asian American man. On Hella Asian, Jason brings up an hot button issue: shoe-free households.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode8.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode8.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode8.m4a" length="32006162" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Jason Shen discusses the results of the 2016 Asian American Man Study, an annual survey of East, Southeast, and South Asian American men. We chat identity, stereotypes, and masculinity. On Hella Asian, Jason espouses shoe-free households.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode8.png"/><itunes:duration>36:38</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[9: Creating Spaces for Women of Color in Tech (ft. Kaitlin Gu)]]></title><description><![CDATA[We chat with Kaitlin Gu, a software engineer at Google and the cofounder of Flawless Hacks, an annual Beyoncé-themed hackathon for women by women. Kaitlin shares her experience as an Asian woman in technology and tells us about how Flawless Hacks started. We discuss her passion for education and how she’s shaped Flawless Hacks to be a collaborative, non-competitive space for women in technology. On Hella Asian, we swap dating expectations our Asian parents have for us.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode9.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode9.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode9.m4a" length="29120564" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>We chat with Kaitlin Gu, a software engineer at Google and cofounder of Flawless Hacks. She shares her experience as an Asian woman in technology and her passion for education. On Hella Asian, we swap parents’ dating expectations.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode9.png"/><itunes:duration>32:05</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[10: Power and Poké: Authenticity and Gentrification of Asian Food (ft. Sonia Chopra)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sonia Chopra, the managing editor of Eater.com, joins us this week to discuss Asian food trends and how certain foods reach the mainstream, who gets to be an authority on ethnic cuisine, and the importance of authenticity in popularizing food that isn’t yours. Why hasn’t Indian food enjoyed the same success and popularity like ramen or matcha? She also dives into Eater’s approach to covering food and its intersections with other aspects of society in diverse and holistic ways. We chat briefly about self-care and the p-word, and Sonia tells us what she does that’s Hella Asian.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode10.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode10.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode10.m4a" length="29381415" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Sonia Chopra, the managing editor of Eater, talks Asian food trends and the importance of authenticity in popularizing food that isn’t yours. She also discusses Eater’s approach to covering food and its intersections in diverse and holistic ways.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode10.png"/><itunes:duration>32:29</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[11: Dumb, Evil, or Both? (ft. Anil Dash)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anil Dash, CEO of FogCreek Software, entrepreneur, activist and writer, joins us on the show to discuss his Indian American identity and how he’s working to make the industry more humane and ethical. Anil talks about raising his son and the role of technology in his family across generations. He dives into how progress happens and the difference between people doing good versus simply wanting to be seen as good. Anil also pops by our Hella Asian segment and prepare yourselves: it’s a juicy one. We also debut a new game segment this week: Appropriation or Appreciation? katie has a personal kimono conundrum.
]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode11.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode11.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode11.m4a" length="44747962" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Anil Dash, CEO of FogCreek Software, discusses his Indian American identity and his work to make the tech industry more humane and ethical. We also debut a new game segment this week: Appropriation or Appreciation? katie has a personal kimono conundrum.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode11.png"/><itunes:duration>50:53</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[12: Indomie, Indo-us (ft. Amy Wibowo)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amy Wibowo joins us this week to chat art, science and everything in between. As founder and CEO of BubbleSort Zines, a monthly zine series illustrating computer science principles, she shares her work to decolonize STEM education and the importance of connecting science with the humanities. She talks about trying to find a home in the US and Indonesia, eventually creating her own. Amy discusses femininity, her approach to social media, and does a deep dive on the ultimate feminist snack: indomie. On Hella Asian, Amy reveals her relationship with her house slippers.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode12.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode12.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode12.m4a" length="27441928" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Amy Wibowo, founder of BubbleSort Zines, wants to combine art and science education. She chats femininity, social media, and dives deep on the ultimate feminist snack: indomie. On Hella Asian, Amy shares her relationship with her house slippers.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode12.png"/><itunes:duration>30:18</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[13: Jū-Ni Dreams of Sushi (ft. Geoffrey Lee)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Geoffrey Lee, executive chef and partner at Jū-Ni, takes us behind the scenes of his Michelin star omakase sushi restaurant in San Francisco. We discuss his experience as a Chinese American sushi chef and what it was like to receive a Michelin star. On Hella Asian, Geoffrey reflects on his subversive and traditional Asian tendencies. And tune into IRL where Nicole walks us through a tour of the Museum of Chinese in America.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode13.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode13.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode13.m4a" length="26543470" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Geoffrey Lee, executive chef at Jū-Ni, takes us behind the scenes of his sushi restaurant. We discuss his experience as a Chinese American sushi chef and getting a Michelin star. Geoffrey drops by Hella Asian, and tune into IRL for a MOCA tour.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode13.png"/><itunes:duration>29:56</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[14: Being Brown in America, the Internet, and Love (ft. Ankur Thakkar)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ankur Thakkar, head of content at Bumpers, talks to us about the internet and how it's helped him get to where he is now. We discussed his time at Vine, its role in democratizing video creation, and what Michelle Obama smells like. We also dive into the different waves of Asian American literature and how it's evolved over time. Ankur tells us about his first novel, which is about being brown in America, love and how the internet has changed how we communicate. On Hella Asian, Ankur shares three unique habits.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode14.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode14.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode14.m4a" length="36842900" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Ankur Thakkar, head of content at Bumpers, talks to us about the internet. We discussed Vine, different waves of Asian American literature and how experimenting with different story forms led to his first novel. Ankur also shares three Hella Asian habits.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode14.png"/><itunes:duration>45:37</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[15: Swipe Right if 大方 [Da Fang] (ft. Lulu Cheng)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lulu Cheng, product manager at Pinterest, talks with us about Asian superstitions around numbers, gift giving, fan death, and more. She dives into how language defines culture — for example, Chinese words that have no real English equivalent. She shares her own progress in learning to speak Chinese with the help of Harry Potter, and we also discuss Lulu’s experience with mental health. On Hella Asian, Lulu shares her favorite part of a meal. Hint: it involves collagen.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode15.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode15.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode15.m4a" length="25261173" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Lulu Cheng, product manager at Pinterest, talks Asian superstitions and how language reflects culture. We discuss Chinese words with no English equivalent and Lulu’s mental health experience. On Hella Asian, she shares her favorite part of a meal.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode15.png"/><itunes:duration>31:03</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[16: Mixed within my Mixedness (ft. Kelsey Cheng)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kelsey Cheng, a potter based in Chicago, talks with us about running a woman-owned business and her side hustle balance. She outlines how her craft and creativity has evolved, and how things like community and social media have influenced her process. She also discusses the ways in which her perspective on her mixed identity have changed over time. On Hella Asian, Kelsey gives us a crash course in bed feng shui.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode16.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode16.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode16.m4a" length="22565298" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Kelsey Cheng, a potter based in Chicago, talks about running a woman-owned business. She outlines how her craft and creativity have evolved and how she thinks about her mixed identity. On Hella Asian, Kelsey gives us a crash course in bed feng shui.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode16.png"/><itunes:duration>27:50</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[17: Soul Searching and Slurping]]></title><description><![CDATA[For the last episode of season one, katie and Nicole reflect on the show so far, share their favorite (and most embarrassing) moments, and discuss their hopes for Sweet and Sour season two and beyond. On Hella Asian, katie brings slurping etiquette to the table.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode17.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode17.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode17.m4a" length="15643435" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>For the last episode of season one, katie and Nicole reflect on the show so far, share their favorite (and most embarrassing) moments, and discuss their hopes for Sweet and Sour season two and beyond. On Hella Asian, katie brings slurping etiquette to the table.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode17.png"/><itunes:duration>17:27</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[18: So What? (ft. Meera Lee Patel)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Author and illustrator Meera Lee Patel discusses her latest book My Friend Fear and how she approaches vulnerability and identity in her art. She shares her pragmatic journey from part-time to full-time artist and talks about the daily philosophies and questions that drive her creativity. On Hella Asian, she shares her suspicious tendencies.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode18.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode18.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode18.m4a" length="52198034" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Author and illustrator Meera Lee Patel discusses her latest book My Friend Fear and how she approaches vulnerability and identity in her art. She shares her pragmatic journey from part-time to full-time artist and talks about the daily philosophies and questions that drive her creativity. On Hella Asian, she shares her suspicious tendencies.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode18.png"/><itunes:duration>28:42</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[19: Dope Artistic Shit (ft. Jenny Yang)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Comedian, writer, and festival organizer Jenny Yang talks about her journey as a recovering overachiever, how she got into comedy, and the way she thinks about her role as an artist and creator. She also discusses the importance of including Asian Americans in the mainstream cultural conversation by creating more touchstones and references through her stand-up, videos, community organizing, and more.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode19.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode19.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode19.m4a" length="24463982" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Comedian, writer, and festival organizer Jenny Yang talks about her journey as a recovering overachiever, how she got into comedy, and the way she thinks about her role as an artist and creator. She also discusses the importance of including Asian Americans in the mainstream cultural conversation by creating more touchstones and references through her stand-up, videos, community organizing, and more.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode19.png"/><itunes:duration>40:20</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[20: Edgy Side (ft. Theresa Lee)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Founder and designer Theresa Lee takes us behind the scenes of her boutique fashion label, Future Glory, a socially conscious maker of handcrafted leather bags and accessories based in San Francisco. Theresa talks about her edgy side, growing up with a chip on her shoulder (and a Tiger Mom), as well as balancing creative risk and business pragmatism. She also discusses how success isn’t guaranteed, and how she plans to out-work everyone.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode20.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode20.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode20.m4a" length="15532014" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Founder and designer Theresa Lee takes us behind the scenes of her boutique fashion label, Future Glory, a socially conscious maker of handcrafted leather bags and accessories based in San Francisco. Theresa talks about her edgy side, growing up with a chip on her shoulder (and a Tiger Mom), as well as balancing creative risk and business pragmatism. She also discusses how success isn’t guaranteed, and how she plans to out-work everyone.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode20.png"/><itunes:duration>25:36</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[21: Embracing Uncertainty (ft. Coleen Baik)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coleen Baik, an independent product designer, illustrator, and advisor, tells us about striking out on her own. She shares her artistic processes, how she’s come to embrace uncertainty, and her experience visiting North Korea as a Korean American. On Hella Asian, she talks about her love for kimchi.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode21.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode21.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode21.m4a" length="65520741" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Coleen Baik, an independent product designer, illustrator, and advisor, tells us about striking out on her own. She shares her artistic processes, how she’s come to embrace uncertainty, and her experience visiting North Korea as a Korean American. On Hella Asian, she talks about her love for kimchi.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode21.png"/><itunes:duration>44:18</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[22: You Do You (ft. Alisha Ramos)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Founder and CEO Alisha Ramos discusses her journey building and and growing Girls’ Night In, a lifestyle brand and community for women who’d rather stay in tonight. Alisha shares how her perspective on her mixed race identity has evolved over time, and how she stays connected with different cultures. She also talks about the importance of strong friendships and prioritizing self-care and mental health. On Hella Asian, Alisha endorses the kimchi at the Whole Foods salad bar.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode22.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode22.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode22.m4a" length="57333880" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Founder and CEO Alisha Ramos discusses her journey building and and growing Girls’ Night In, a lifestyle brand and community for women who’d rather stay in tonight. Alisha shares how her perspective on her mixed race identity has evolved over time, and how she stays connected with different cultures. She also talks about the importance of strong friendships and prioritizing self-care and mental health. On Hella Asian, Alisha endorses the kimchi at the Whole Foods salad bar.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode22.png"/><itunes:duration>38:46</itunes:duration></item><item><title><![CDATA[23: Trial and Error (ft. Katherine Jin)]]></title><description><![CDATA[COO and cofounder Katherine Jin tells us about the evolution of Kinnos, a biotech company that’s raising the standard of infectious disease decontamination. Katherine also discusses her experience in the startup space as an Asian American woman, entrepreneur, and inventor. On Hella Asian, Katherine shares her habit of saving food.]]></description><link>http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode23.m4a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode23.m4a</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[katie zhu and Nicole Zhu]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/audio/sweet-and-sour-episode23.m4a" length="69452814" type="audio/m4a"/><itunes:author>katie zhu and Nicole Zhu</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>COO and cofounder Katherine Jin tells us about the evolution of Kinnos, a biotech company that’s raising the standard of infectious disease decontamination. Katherine also discusses her experience in the startup space as an Asian American woman, entrepreneur, and inventor. On Hella Asian, Katherine shares her habit of saving food.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:image href="http://sweetandsour.fm/feed/assets/img/episode23.png"/><itunes:duration>46:58</itunes:duration></item></channel></rss>